Schneider, Anna Weinstock Audio Tapes 5143 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Anna Weinstock Schneider Audio Tapes
1969-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Weinstock Schneider, Anna
5143 AV
2.56 cubic feet
2.6 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
7592577
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
C. Eastman, March 09, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, November 01, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Schneider was the first woman Commissioner of Conciliation, U.S. Department of Labor appointed in 1922. A member of several minimum wage boards in Massachusetts, lobbyist for labor legislation in Massachusetts and organizer for the Massachusetts Suffrage Association, she was also active in union activities as President of Boston Women's Trade Union League and organizer for the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5143: Anna Weinstock Schneider Papers 5143 mf: Anna Weinstock Schneider Papers on Microfilm
Schnieder, Anna W. (Anna Weinstock)
7592577
- Tape #1 (June 13, 1969), 1 (Box 1)
- Tape #2 (6/26/1970), 2 (Box 1)
- Tape #3 (6/30/1970), 3 (Box 1)
- Tape #4 (7/1/1970), 4 (Box 1)
- Tape #5 (June 17, 1969), 5 (Box 1)
- Tape #6 (7/7/1970), 6 (Box 1)
- Tape #7 (June 20, 1969), 7 (Box 1)
- Tape #8 (June 20, 1969), 8 (Box 1)
- Tape #9 (July 9, 1969), 9 (Box 1)
- Tape #10 (July 9, 1970), 10 (Box 1)
- Tape #11 (July 9, 1969), 11 (Box 1)
- Tape #12 (July 9, 1970), 12 (Box 1)
- Tape #13 (July 16, 1969), 13 (Box 1)
- Tape #14 (July 16, 1969), 14 (Box 1)
- Tape #15 (July 16, July 23), 1 (Box 2)
- Tape #16 (July 23), 2 (Box 2)
- tape #17 (July 23), 3 (Box 2)
- tape #19 (August 7, 1969), 4 (Box 2)
- tape #20 (August 7, 1969), 5 (Box 2)
- tape #21 (August 7,1969), 6 (Box 2)
- tape #22 (August 7, 1969), 7 (Box 2)
- tape #18 (July 29, 1970), 8 (Box 2)
- tape #1, 1 (Box 3)
- tape #2, 1 (Box 4)
- tape #3, 1 (Box 5)
- tape #4, 1 (Box 6)
- tape #5, 1 (Box 7)
- tape #6, 1 (Box 8)
- tape #7, 1 (Box 9)
- tape #8, 1 (Box 10)
- tape #9, 1 (Box 11)
- tape #10, 1 (Box 12)
- tape #11, 1 (Box 13)
- tape #12, 1 (Box 14)
- tape #13, 1 (Box 15)
- tape #14, 1 (Box 16)